agropages.com 2009-12-28

# Agropages.com, agrochemical online B2B marketplace!

  |  |  |  | 

General Terms

| 

Rules of using AgroPages.com

| 

Privacy

| 

Liability

| 

Registered Users

| 

Gold Member  
  
---|---|---|---|---|---  
| 

**User Agreement**

We, AgroPages.com establish the policies that help to create a global Agro- chemical e-marketplace with safe, fair and convenience trading environment for all AgroPages.com family members. Before you use our services, please read this Agreement carefully and whatever kind of users you are, we regard respectively that you have read and you agree all the terms of this Agreement. 

We may amend the terms of this Agreement by posting the amended terms on this Site without notice. 

The "User Agreement " describes the terms and conditions applicable to your use of the AgroPages.com website which is identified by the uniform resource locator www.agropages.com (the " Site " ). This Agreement is entered into between you as the user of the Site (the " User " ) and us (AgroPages.com).   
  
---  
   
|    
---  
  
**●** We respect the laws of countries including federal, state or provincial and local governments. Any items that may offend those laws including copyright, trademark and other Intellectual Property Protection laws are prohibited and restricted while listing or selling by any users on the site. Those items listing on the site that may violate the laws would be removed without notice. We reserve the right to impose additional restrictions and prohibitions. 

● We are not the expert in your intellectual property rights, and we cannot verify that the users of our online marketplace have the right to sell the goods. Also, we are not an arbiter or judge to deal with any intellectual property disputes; therefore, we would not endorse a claim of infringement. However, we regard the removal of a listing as a prudential matter and we would determine to cancel the listing only when the appropriate legal document has been shown to us certifying the truth against such kind of offence. We appreciate your assistance in identifying those intellectual infringements. 

●  Please report problems, offensive content, and policy violation to us. Without limiting other remedies, we may limit, suspend, or terminate our service and user accounts, prohibit access to our website, delay or remove hosted content, and take technical and legal steps to keep users off if we think that they are creating problems, or acting inconsistently with the letter or spirit of our policies. We also reserve the right to cancel unconfirmed accounts or accounts that have been inactive for over 12 months. 

●  When you give us content, you grant us a non-exclusive, worldwide, perpetual, irrevocable, royalty-free, sub-licensable right to use the copyright, publicity, database rights you have in the content, in any media known now or in the future. 

●  Each of our policies may be change from time to time. Changes take effect when we post them on the Site. When using particular services on our website, you are subject to any posted policies or rules applicable to services you use through the Site, which may be posted from time to time. All such policies or rules are hereby incorporated into this Agreement.   

**2\. Rules of using AgroPages.com**  
  
|    
---  
  
**While using the Site, you will not**

● use of Profanity, HTML and JavaScript, Links, Spamming, Chain letters and other inappropriate practices for the purpose of attracting buyers; 

● distribute viruses or any other technologies that may harm the Site or the interests or property of the site users; 

● post content or items in an inappropriate category or areas on the Site; 

● violate any laws, third party rights, or our policies. 

● use the Site if you are not able to form legally binding contracts, are under the age of 18, or are temporarily or indefinitely suspended from the Site; 

● post false, inaccurate, fraud, misleading, defamatory, or libelous content including personal information; 

● transfer your account including feedback and User ID to another party without our consent; 

● copy, modify, or distribute content from the Site and AgroPages.com's copyrights and trademarks; 

● use the Site to copy, modify or distribute content from the Site users' copyrights and trademarks. 

● collect or harvest information about the Site users including email address, without their consent.   

|    
---  
  
**3.1 Private information we may collect**

**●** Registration Information 

At the time you register to become a Registered User of the Site, you will be asked to complete a registration form which requires you to provide information such as your name, address, phone/fax number, email address and other personal information as well as information about your business. 

●  Publishing Information 

If you submit any information to AgroPages.com and to be published on the Site through the publishing tools, including but not limited to Company Profile, Product Catalog, Trade Leads, you agree to give consent on the publication of such information. 

●  Payment Information 

If you establish a credit account for online transaction purpose or purchase of our service, we may collect additional information, including billing information, credit card number, expiration dates and other financial information. 

● Statistical Information 

We may gather aggregate statistical information about the Site and the User, such as IP addresses, browser software, operating system, pages viewed, number of sessions, unique visitors and etc.. 

**3.2 How we use Private information**

**●** As the User, you agree that we may use your personal information to: 

◆ provide the customer services and support your request; 

◆ resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems; 

◆ prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our User Agreement; 

◆ customize, measure and improve our services, content and advertising; 

◆ tell you about targeted marketing, service updates, and promotional offers based on your communication preferences; Compare information for accuracy, and verify it with third parties. 

● We don't sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. We may combine your information with information we collect from other companies and use it to improve and personalize our services, content and advertising. If you don't wish to receive marketing communications from us, simply give us a notice by the ways we provide to you for contact to us. 

● We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that a listing or other content violates the rights of others, or protect anyone's rights, property, or safety. 

● We may also share your personal information with: 

◆ Members of our corporate family to help detect and prevent potentially illegal acts and provide joint content and services (for example, registration, transactions and customer support). Our corporate affiliates will send marketing communications only to users who request these services. 

◆ Service providers under contract who help with our business operations (such as fraud investigations, bill collection, affiliate and rewards programs and co-branded credit cards). 

◆ Other third parties to whom you explicitly ask us to send your information (or about whom you are otherwise explicitly notified and consent to when using a specific service). 

◆ Law enforcement or other governmental officials, in response to a verified request relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity. In such events, we will disclose information relevant to the investigation, such as name, city, state or province, zip code, telephone number, email address, User ID history, IP address, fraud complaints, and listing history etc. 

◆ Other business entities, should we plan to merge with or be acquired by that business entity. 

● Without limiting the above, in an effort to respect your privacy and our ability to keep our community free from bad actors, we will not otherwise disclose your personal information to law enforcement, other government officials, or other third parties without a subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal procedure, except when we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss or to report suspected illegal activity. 

● We cannot guarantee the privacy or security of your information and therefore we encourage you to evaluate the privacy and security policies of your trading partner before entering into a transaction and choosing to share your information. When users are involved in a transaction, they may have access to each other's name, User ID, email address and other contact and shipping information. In all cases, you must give other users a chance to remove themselves from your database and a chance to review what information you have collected about them. 

**3.3 Cookies**

**●** We use "cookies" on certain of our pages to help analyze our web page flow; Customize our services, content and advertising; measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety. 

**3.4 Security**

**●** Your private information especially your Registration Information, Publishing Information and Payment Information can be viewed and edited through your Account which is protected by Password. We hold reasonable security methods to prevent from unauthorized access, store and maintain data accuracy and ensure correct use of information. 

● We recommend that you do not divulge your Password to anyone. Our personnel will never ask you for your Password whenever in unsolicited phone call or e-mail. If you share a computer with others, you should not choose to save your log-in information (e.g., User ID and Password) on the computer. Remember to sign out of your Account and close your browser window when you have finished your session. 

● No data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be perfectly secured. As a result, no one including ourselves can absolutely ensure or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us and you may take your own risk while doing so. 

**3.5 Third Parties**

● Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document addresses only the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. If you disclose your information to others, whether they are buyers or sellers on our websites or other sites throughout the internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. We do not control the privacy policies of third parties, and you are subject to the privacy policies of those third parties where applicable.   
   
|    
---  
  
**●** We, AgroPages.com will not take any responsibilities for any Users' actions or inactions, including things they post. AgroPages.com provides an electronic web-based platform for exchanging information between buyers and suppliers at anytime, from anywhere, for a variety of products and services. We are not involved in the actual transaction between buyers and sellers. We have no control over and do not guarantee the quality, safety or legality of items advertised, the truth or accuracy of listings, the ability of sellers to sell items, the ability of buyers to pay for items, or that a buyer or seller will actually complete a transaction. We do not transfer legal ownership of items from the seller to buyer. Further, we cannot guarantee continuous or secure access to our services, and operation of our websites may be interfered with by numerous parties outside of our control. Accordingly, to the extent legally permitted, we exclude all implied warranties, terms and conditions. We are not liable for any loss of money, goodwill, or reputation, or any special, indirect, or consequential damages arising out of your use of the Site. However, if we are found to be liable, our liability to you or to any third party is limited to the greater of (a) the total fees you paid to us in the 6 months prior to the action giving rise to the liability, and (b) USD$350. 

● You will indemnify and hold us harmless from any claim or demand, including reasonable attorneys' fee, made by any third party due to or arising out of your breach of this Agreement, or your violation of any laws or the rights of a third party.   

| 

**●** The User who has filled out an on-line Registration Form on the Site and been approved by AgroPages.com is a Registered User. AgroPages.com will establish an account for each Registered User and a User ID will be assigned to the Registered User with their own password for log-in access to its own Account. 

● By becoming a Registered User, you consent to the inclusion of your personal data in our Global Buyer Database and authorize AgroPages.com to share such information with other Users. 

● AgroPages.com may suspend or terminate a Registered User's Account or Email Account at any time by giving no less than 24-hour notice to the Registered User. However, the notice is not required for such kind of termination if (a) there is any breach of this Agreement by the Registered User; or (b) It is reasonable for Agropages.com to suspect that such information provided by a Registered User is untrue, inaccurate, not current or complete, or (c) AgroPages.com believes that the Registered User's actions may cause financial loss or legal liability to Us or our affiliates, or to such a Registered User itself, or to AgroPages.com's other Users. 

● You must be a Registered User in order to post information on the Site using the self-help submit and edit tools provided through the Site. 

● Each User hereby represents, warrants and agrees to (a) provide AgroPages.com with true, accurate, current and complete information to be displayed on the Site and (b) maintain and promptly amend all information to keep it true, accurate, current and complete. 

● Each User hereby represents, warrants and agrees that he or she has obtained all necessary third party's copyright, trademark, trade secret or patent license and permission, or such other licenses or permissions as may be required in connection with any other personal or proprietary rights of any third parties (including but not limited to rights of personality and rights of privacy), for any material or information it posts on the Site or provides to AgroPages.com or authorizes Us to display. 

● Each User hereby represents, warrants and agrees that he or she shall be solely responsible for ensuring that any material or information it posts on the Site or provides to Agropages.com or authorizes Agropages.com to display does not, and that the product represented thereby does not violate any Third Party's Rights, or it is posted with the permission of the owner(s) of such rights. 

● Each User hereby represents, warrants and agrees that he or she has the right to manufacture, offer, sell, import and distribute the products which are offered and displayed on the Site, and that such manufacture, offer, sale, importation and/or distribution of those products do not violate any Third Party Rights. 

● Each User hereby represents, warrants and agrees that information submitted to AgroPages.com for display on the Site shall not contain fraudulent information or make fraudulent offers of items or involve the sale or attempted sale of counterfeit or stolen items or items whose sales and/or marketing is prohibited by applicable law, or otherwise promote other illegal activities; shall not be part of a scheme to defraud other Users of the Site or for any other unlawful purpose. 

● Each User hereby represents, warrants and agrees that information submitted to AgroPages.com for display on the Site shall not be obscene or contain or infer any pornography or sex-related merchandising or any other content or otherwise promotes sexually explicit materials or is otherwise harmful to minors. 

● Each User hereby represents, warrants and agrees that information submitted to AgroPages.com for display on the Site shall not promote discrimination based on race, sex, religion, nationality, disability, or age. 

● Each User hereby represents, warrants and agrees that information submitted to AgroPages.com for display on the Site shall not contain any material that constitutes unauthorized advertising or harassment (including but not limited to spamming), invades anyone's privacy or encourages conduct that would constitute a criminal offence, give rise to civil liability, or otherwise violate any law or regulation. 

● Each User hereby represents, warrants and agrees that information submitted to AgroPages.com for display on the Site shall not solicit business from any Users in connection with a commercial activity that competes with AgroPages.com. 

● Each User hereby represents, warrants and agrees that information submitted to AgroPages.com for display on the Site shall not contain any computer viruses or other destructive devices and codes that have the effect of damaging, interfering with or intercepting any software or hardware systems, data or personal information. 

● Each User hereby represents, warrants and agrees that information submitted to AgroPages.com for display on the Site shall not li nk directly or indirectly to or include descriptions of goods or services that are prohibited under this Agreement. 

● The Users are solely responsible for all of the terms and conditions of the transactions conducted on, through or as a result of use of the Site, including, without limitation, terms regarding payment, returns, warranties, shipping, insurance, fees, taxes, title, licenses, fines, permits, handling, transportation and storage.   
  
---  

**●** We, AgroPages.com, provide Premier Services to group of our special clients. We regard this kind of client as the Gold Member. 

● AgroPages.com reserves the right to deny, suspend or terminate Premier Services to any Users for whatever reason in order to protect the interests of AgroPages.com. 

● The Premier service for Gold Members may be ruled by the additional terms and conditions besides all the Terms of Policies in the previous paragraph of this Agreement. The additional terms and conditions for the Gold Member are also part of this Agreement and AgroPages.com reserves the right to amend these Terms and Conditions.
